{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.93","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030256591","data":{"timestamp":" 947030256591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030276229","data":{"timestamp":" 947030276229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 7431b18d-9ca3-45ab-a813-e8d438cbc105"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030333865","data":{"timestamp":" 947030333865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 7431b18d-9ca3-45ab-a813-e8d438cbc105"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030333949","data":{"timestamp":" 947030333949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 7431b18d-9ca3-45ab-a813-e8d438cbc105"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030374670","data":{"timestamp":" 947030374670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_f_m_h"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030381297","data":{"timestamp":" 947030381296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_j_h"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030387930","data":{"timestamp":" 947030387930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_f_m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030395412","data":{"timestamp":" 947030395411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_f_m"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030402044","data":{"timestamp":" 947030402044"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_r_u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030408711","data":{"timestamp":" 947030408711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_k_h"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030416204","data":{"timestamp":" 947030416204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_k_h"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030422843","data":{"timestamp":" 947030422842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_l_h_b"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030429488","data":{"timestamp":" 947030429488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_i_n_h"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030436123","data":{"timestamp":" 947030436123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_j_f_h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030442773","data":{"timestamp":" 947030442772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_h_y_g"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030449440","data":{"timestamp":" 947030449440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_r_h_u"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:H..H.all.10.rand.say.46","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030461549","data":{"timestamp":" 947030461548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 9de2cb78-d816-4dbe-ae3f-d6ea1921cfc9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_H..H.all.10.rand.say.46"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_r_h_u"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030476444","data":{"timestamp":" 947030476444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030479008","data":{"timestamp":" 947030479008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030480557","data":{"timestamp":" 947030480557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030482674","data":{"timestamp":" 947030482673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030484276","data":{"timestamp":" 947030484275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030486935","data":{"timestamp":" 947030486935"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030488545","data":{"timestamp":" 947030488544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030490548","data":{"timestamp":" 947030490547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030492144","data":{"timestamp":" 947030492143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030494448","data":{"timestamp":" 947030494447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030496047","data":{"timestamp":" 947030496046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030500625","data":{"timestamp":" 947030500624"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030502228","data":{"timestamp":" 947030502228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030504482","data":{"timestamp":" 947030504482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030506067","data":{"timestamp":" 947030506066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030516039","data":{"timestamp":" 947030516038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030517663","data":{"timestamp":" 947030517662"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030521709","data":{"timestamp":" 947030521709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" START_I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030524176","data":{"timestamp":" 947030524175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030525751","data":{"timestamp":" 947030525751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030529515","data":{"timestamp":" 947030529515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030531132","data":{"timestamp":" 947030531131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030533643","data":{"timestamp":" 947030533643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030535245","data":{"timestamp":" 947030535245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030539932","data":{"timestamp":" 947030539932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030541520","data":{"timestamp":" 947030541519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030543767","data":{"timestamp":" 947030543767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030545363","data":{"timestamp":" 947030545363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030548151","data":{"timestamp":" 947030548150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030549772","data":{"timestamp":" 947030549771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030551965","data":{"timestamp":" 947030551964"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030553562","data":{"timestamp":" 947030553562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030556737","data":{"timestamp":" 947030556736"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030558344","data":{"timestamp":" 947030558343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030560686","data":{"timestamp":" 947030560686"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030562278","data":{"timestamp":" 947030562277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030565703","data":{"timestamp":" 947030565702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030567299","data":{"timestamp":" 947030567298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030569492","data":{"timestamp":" 947030569492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030571095","data":{"timestamp":" 947030571094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030575287","data":{"timestamp":" 947030575287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030576897","data":{"timestamp":" 947030576896"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030580460","data":{"timestamp":" 947030580460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030582062","data":{"timestamp":" 947030582062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030585159","data":{"timestamp":" 947030585158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030586726","data":{"timestamp":" 947030586725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030591293","data":{"timestamp":" 947030591293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030592844","data":{"timestamp":" 947030592844"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030596877","data":{"timestamp":" 947030596876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030598898","data":{"timestamp":" 947030598898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030598973","data":{"timestamp":" 947030598973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030628420","data":{"timestamp":" 947030628420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a4bc0ed8-f6d7-44e2-94c2-17c49de3e6be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030648791","data":{"timestamp":" 947030648791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030652579","data":{"timestamp":" 947030652579"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030656838","data":{"timestamp":" 947030656838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030660484","data":{"timestamp":" 947030660483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030664325","data":{"timestamp":" 947030664325"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030667656","data":{"timestamp":" 947030667656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030671684","data":{"timestamp":" 947030671684"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030694966","data":{"timestamp":" 947030694966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030698672","data":{"timestamp":" 947030698672"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030702599","data":{"timestamp":" 947030702599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030706910","data":{"timestamp":" 947030706909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030710581","data":{"timestamp":" 947030710581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030714245","data":{"timestamp":" 947030714245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030718324","data":{"timestamp":" 947030718324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030721767","data":{"timestamp":" 947030721767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030725116","data":{"timestamp":" 947030725116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030728548","data":{"timestamp":" 947030728548"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030732338","data":{"timestamp":" 947030732338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030735755","data":{"timestamp":" 947030735755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030739682","data":{"timestamp":" 947030739681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030743992","data":{"timestamp":" 947030743992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030747400","data":{"timestamp":" 947030747400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030773884","data":{"timestamp":" 947030773883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030777632","data":{"timestamp":" 947030777631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030783373","data":{"timestamp":" 947030783372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" a6fcd8e5-fd61-41fd-a2f7-e5470af4e2b7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030823878","data":{"timestamp":" 947030823877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030834607","data":{"timestamp":" 947030834606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030839362","data":{"timestamp":" 947030839362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030843811","data":{"timestamp":" 947030843810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030878781","data":{"timestamp":" 947030878781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030890485","data":{"timestamp":" 947030890485"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030893805","data":{"timestamp":" 947030893804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030900806","data":{"timestamp":" 947030900806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030904668","data":{"timestamp":" 947030904668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030943570","data":{"timestamp":" 947030943570"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030947653","data":{"timestamp":" 947030947653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030960653","data":{"timestamp":" 947030960653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030965171","data":{"timestamp":" 947030965171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030972499","data":{"timestamp":" 947030972499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031002275","data":{"timestamp":" 947031002275"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031014491","data":{"timestamp":" 947031014491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031026289","data":{"timestamp":" 947031026289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031030611","data":{"timestamp":" 947031030611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031048223","data":{"timestamp":" 947031048223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947031049483","data":{"timestamp":" 947031049483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025724"," gameId":" 0ccdf4db-2151-48c1-8be2-f5c4fa9a8c1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}